

Supun Praneeth

Full-stack developer



Summery

I enjoy turning complex problems into simple and beautiful codes. I started coding 10 years ago when I was in school and I have 4 years of professional experience in creating web based projects in multiple industries such as leisure, education, travel etc. I am eager to learn new technologies and currently learning NodeJs(Express, Meteor, Sail.Js) and Python. I am also a big fan of open-source development and looking forward to work on open source projects.



Experience

2016-08 Present

Tech Lead

Apple Tech Labs

Responsibilities:

- Design, develop, test and implement new applications.
- Train interns
- Clearly and regularly communicate with management and technical support colleagues.
- Managing servers (e-mail, database and web servers).
- Design and update software database.
- Analyze user requirements and convert requirements to design documents.

2014-10-2015-08

Full-stack developer

Apple Holidays

Responsibilities:

- Develop, test and implement new applications.
- Customizing systems/application made by company.
- Design and update software database.



Latest Projects

2016-08 Present

Real Time Holidays Package Creator (V2)

Web application that creates holiday packages for multiple countries including Sri Lanka, Malaysia, Indonesia, Thailand and Singapore. See full details at: supun.xyz

Task:

- Planning destinations, shortest path, nearest airports etc.
- Booking cheapest hotels and own accommodations.
- Booking restaurants.
- Driver registration and allocation.

2018 Present

Leaflet Bezier

Leaflet: Draws a Bézier line between two points with an animated flight object.





Personal Info

Phone

(+94) 774 637514

Portfolio

supun.xyz

E-mail

hello@supun.xyz

Date of birth

1991-04-12

Marital status

Single

Github

github.com/spmsupun

LinkedIn

LinkedIn.com/in/spmsupun

Stackoverflow

stackoverflow.com/cv/supun



Skills

PHP (Laravel)

Javascript (ES6)

CSS/SCSS





2018 Present

JSQL

PHP package(Composer) that convert Json object to SQL with relationships.

Education

2014 Present

Bachelor of Computer Science

Following BSC CS at National School of Business Management (NSBM) which is affiliated with University College Dublin (UCD) in Ireland.

ΑŻ

Languages

English

Upper Intermediate

Sinhala

Native

References

Thiraj priyadharshana

Software Engineer 121 Hunupitiya Lake Rd, Colombo 02, Sri Lanka thirajpriyadharshana@gmail.com (+94) 714 542601

Desmond Bartholomeusz

Senior Manager - Development 148, Aluthmawatha Road, Colombo 15, Sri Lanka product@appleholidaysds.com (+94) 703 653343



Frameworks / Tools

Laravel 5+

2+ year experience

jQuery

7+ years experience

Bootstrap 3/4

2+ years experience

Angular 5+

Learning

Express.js 4

Learning

PhpStorm

1+ year experience

Linux (SSH)

1+ year experience

GIT

2+ year experience

Docker

6 months experience

AWS

Learning